

Lagos, Nigeria, 07067069561, chinedugabriel29@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a front-end developer focused on crafting clean & user-friendly experiences, I am passionate about building excellent software that improves the lives of those around me and I am ready to take on challenges using problem-solving and task prioritization skills to help the team succeed.

EXPERIENCE

HR Consultant

January 2022 - May 2022

APPWORLD | Lagos, Nigeria

- Brought in highly qualified applicants, and targeted recruitment strategies on key candidate pools.
- Addressed employee relations issues, harassment allegations, and work complaints.
- Performed manual labor tasks to detailed instructions from supervisors.

IT Consultant

January 2020 - February 2021

Nigerian Institute For Industrial Security | Lagos, Nigeria

- Built automation into technical systems to help with repetitive tasks.
- · Configured software solutions to meet customers' business process requirements.
- Employed consultative skills to assess user needs and develop and deliver technical training.
- Followed up and handled inbound leads with online web sales and marketing channels.
- Kept organization at forefront of technological advances, tracking new technologies and integrating best-fit options.
- Improved system usability by consulting with end-users to identify deficiencies and missing features.

Web Designer

January 2018 - February 2019

APPWORLD | Lagos, Nigeria

- Assessed complex technical designs to opportunities for simplification and user satisfaction improvements.
- Prepared website low-fidelity wireframes and high-fidelity mockups for developers and project managers.

- Updated design advice based on current web trends, technology changes, and style improvements.
- Improved usability and appearance of eCommerce, booking, and other site features.
- · Developed design ideas in Adobe Photoshop for different stages of web design and development.
- Created highly responsive and scalable web applications for use in different industries and client environments. website created accessible web front-end user interface for new or existing E with a combination of HTML, CSS, and JAVASCRIPT

Computer Systems Administrator

February 2017 - February 2019

APPWORLD | Lagos, Nigeria

- Supported users with training, technical assistance, and network improvements.
- Helped technical team install, configure and customize company-wide systems.
- · Corrected hardware, software, and network connectivity issues by diagnosing faults and completing skilled repairs.
- Prevented data loss with regular backups and sound disaster recovery processes.
- Monitor system performance and maintain systems according to requirements

SKILLS

 Proficient knowledge of HTMI

Proficient knowledge of CSS
Proficient knowledge of

JAVASCRIPT

Proficient With Wordpress
Proficient With Figma

 Proficient With Affinity Photo & Designer

Employee relations

Policy development

Retention management

Recruitment and hiring

Benefits administration

Good communication

Issue troubleshooting

Team work

EDUCATION

BSC HONS Computer Science (Second Class Upper Division) - Computer Science

November 2017

ECOLE SUPERIESURE DE MANAGEMENT UNIVERSITIE,, Benin Republic